{
    "subject": "Peter_Sollett",
    "predicate": "created",
    "object": "Raising_Victor_Vargas",
    "human_readable": "Peter Sollett created Raising Victor Vargas.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.7262213826179504,
            "question": "Are there any other movies directed by Peter Sollett besides Raising Victor Vargas?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6947391033172607,
            "question": "What year was Raising Victor Vargas released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6406116485595703,
            "question": "Who directed the movie Raising Victor Vargas?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6193239688873291,
            "question": "What is the genre of Raising Victor Vargas?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5944961905479431,
            "question": "What type of work did Peter Sollett produce?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.591768205165863,
            "question": "What is the plot of Raising Victor Vargas?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5813570618629456,
            "question": "What is the name of the movie that Peter Sollett created?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3548075258731842,
            "question": "Is Peter Sollett known for directing movies?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3181626498699188,
            "question": "Is Peter Sollett a well-known director?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.20027507841587067,
            "question": "Can you name a movie directed by Peter Sollett?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Peter Sollett created Raising Victor Vargas.",
            "html": "yago_15779_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Peter Sollett a well-known director?",
            "html": "yago_15779_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Peter Sollett known for directing movies?",
            "html": "yago_15779_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of the movie that Peter Sollett created?",
            "html": "yago_15779_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_15779_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_15779_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_15779_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_15779_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_15779_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_15779_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_15779_61.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_15779_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_15779_88.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_15779_91.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the response in the structured JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provided contain multiple references to a film called \"Raising Victor Vargas\", and they all mention Peter Sollett as the director of this film. This information supports the triple that Peter Sollett created Raising Victor Vargas."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents clearly state that Peter Sollett directed and wrote the film \"Raising Victor Vargas\" (2002), supporting the given triple."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}